Tokimeki Balameter Jochon TV
Yes, so today is something a little bit different from the usual
The center game from Mr. Cucumber
My name is Prince Shotoku
Today, we are going to praise each other's favorite parts, or rather, we are going to praise each other a lot about the members sitting here right now, and I'm going to ask Pio to tell me what he likes about me.
We are going to play a game called "Shotoku Taishi" in which we praise each other and Pio-chan asks us what we like about each other.
Let's see how many you can guess.
Five of us will say what we like about Pio at the same time.
I'll ask Pio to guess all five.
What is it?
I think I got more than that.
There's five of me.
That's plenty.
I'm a little nervous.
We all have to say it as loud as we can.
I'll say it louder.
You'll have to match.
Ahhh!
Thank you.
Okay, one time, say it with your favorite fruit.
Fruit.
Okay.
Strawberry!
No way!
This is hard.
And did you say omelette rice?
Jan is next to me.
Jan next to me.
But you know what? I got it.
How many did you get?
Something about strawberries and...
Strawberries and what?
Strawberries is all I got.
I'm too big for this.
I'll make them a little bigger.
It's not that easy, I promise.
Shall we go for the real thing?
Miyu's favorite part.
I'm not afraid of you.
Don't share.
Let's imagine you're a decimalist.
Decimalist
What do you like about Hiyori?
Yes, I do.
Here we go
Seino
It doesn't take much at all.
Oh, no!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
This is really hard.
Can you try one more time?
Think about it one more time.
I know, I know. One time out.
I only heard one.
What is it?
Twintails.
Did anyone say that?
Twintails look good on you.
Oh, that's right.
Oh.
Okay, one more.
Four more.
Uh, but... you know, Aki was making some kind of noise.
Everyone's voice...
Like everyone else's.
I thought it was too quiet, so I lowered my voice.
What?
What's wrong?
I was pretty loud.
I couldn't hear you at all.
I only had one more coming in.
That's all that came in.
But, hey...
I mean, you're supposed to say five.
Okay, can I try one more?
Can I say it louder?
Like, uh...
Okay. - Okay.
Okay, can you do it again a second time, please?
Okay.
Your Instagram is so cool.
Stylish Insta.
Insta is fashionable.
I heard you.
I hear you!
I hear it.
But I can't hear anything else.
But I don't hear anything else.
I can't hear you.
Miss.
I'm so deaf.
Oh, hey.
I interfered.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Uh...
Julia, I let you play.
I'm sorry.Sorry.
Yeah. Bye.
Three more to go.
Wow, what did I say?
Mm-hmm.
Hard to tell.
It's something, Aki-chan said it too.
Eh, hey, surprisingly, these two are young.
Maybe because, you know, they have ears on both sides.
That's right.
Right.
And Hitokotocha-chan's voice maybe a little bit like hers, right?
Wow, what did I say?
But I'm saying.
I like it here.
What?
What does she always say?
Oh, I'm saying it.
I wonder...
It's Hime. It's Hime, isn't it?
What do you like?
That?
Eeeee!
I wonder.
What do you like about Hinokashu?
Oh, but everyone likes everything, so it's okay to say anything.
Well, yeah.
I'm going to give my chance points.
I think I might be a little bit hot here.
I think I'm hot... by the way, I think I'm hot...
Stop, stop, stop.
Stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it, I'm getting embarrassed.
Okay, first of all, Yahitaka...
Pio's...
I like Pio's kindness.
He's cute.
I don't like it.
I like him.
He's cute.
I thought I said that.
The person who heard you said that.
You're so sweet.
I think about that all the time.
Oharu...
Eh.
I wonder what it is.
I like her gentle singing voice.
All of them are gentle anyway.
Aki-chan...
I like Hiyori's smile.
Yes, yes, yes.
I like that one too.
Oh, I liked it. I like what you just said.
I totally like it.
So, how about it?
Yes, I like it.
So, correct answer?
Correct?
Let's give the correct answer.
Yes, I like her twin-tail hair. I like the way you wear twin-tail hair.
Yes.
I like Chiya's stylish instagram.
That's 2 points.
I like the way she laughs.
Ah~~.
You're saying quite a bit.
I heard you a little.
You're really saying it.
You're lying.
There he is.
Did you see the way he laughed?
I guess the impact drowned it out.
I heard you.
I'm really saying it.
Laughter.
I said, "Meh!" I said, "Meh!
Meh!
Is one word too hard to say?
Sure it is.
Bekka.
I like it when you wait for me.
Cute!
You waited for me?
Okay, then.
So, Yu-chan gets 2 points.
This is a good game.
It's fun.
Interesting.
This position is interesting, too.
Okay, next is Aki-chan.
You don't need to adjust the voice part, do you?
Oh, I see.
My favorite color.
Let's see more than before.
Ready?
Pink!
How's that?
Red, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink.
All of them are pink except for the red one.It's pink except for the red.
It's pink, isn't it?
Pink is so strong.
Pink!
I was surprised that everyone was so excited about the pink.
I'd like to set a tone like this.
Please do.
Here we go.
Let's go! Zero chalk!
Seriously?
You just figured that out?
I just figured it out. I just figured it out.
What did I just say?
All I heard was your voice.
Sei...
Sei-sei-sei!
pi
Sorry, Aki-chan.
Many people call me Pi.
Pi?
No, it's not.
Huh?
A lot of people say "Pi".
Sei.
Sei...
Sei
Sei kakuun
I, I could hear one.
Maybe Julia's.
Okay, I got it.
The one next to it.
Easy to understand.
Let's split them up, people.
A little lower.
Split them apart.
Let's split them up.
Okay.
Okay, we'll go high.
Okay, low.
Here we go.
Ready.
What?
Oh, no.
I only recognized Hiyori.
You got it?
The sensitive part.
Penpan.
Oh my God.
You sound really weird.
What's he saying?
She has a really weird voice.
Julia's voice is weird, too.
Okay, I get it.
Don't you get it?
I like it.
I guess we'll just have to go with Aki-chan here.
Let's take a wild guess.
Uh...
Well, Kanami...
Huh?
Hey, hey, hey, on camera.
Just one last thing.
You're all so cute, I just want to see your faces.
I want to see their faces.
I don't know.
Where's your smile?
Smile?
Oh, no.
I like smiles.
And...
Yeah.
I don't know.
The fastest place to record.
It's fast, for sure.
It's certainly fast.
Indeed.
Very fast.
Soon.
It's like, even if you can read this, it's immediate.
It starts right away.
Hito-chan...
So, what is it?
What is it?
It's hard for me.
Difficult? Do you always tell me?
Maybe not, but you do.
I heard you on the radio, and you said I was kind.
I mean, she's kind... kind... kind...
That's what she said.
I like her.
I like you.
What? It's true!
Oharu-chan always says it's a facial expression.
But it's not a facial expression.
That's for sure.No doubt about it.
Yellow is a good color for you.
Okay, answers, please.
Let's start with Pio.
Sensitive.
Lovely clothes.
Ah...
I don't know.
Um... that's how you say it.
Your clothes are cute.
I knew that.
They're always telling me.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's real.
He's fine.
That's easy to understand.
I made it easy to understand.
I was going to say heroine, but...
It's hard.
It's difficult.
I think a lower voice would be easier to understand.
I see.
Then, Aki-chan, you get one point.
One point.
Okay, then.
Are we done?
Let's go.
Okay.
Cachaça's place.
I don't know.
Cachaça part...
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Oh, no.
Why?
picky eater
Hey...
He didn't paint it. - What?
I don't know why. It sounded like a cacher.
One more time, please. Ready?
Beauty and the Child of the Mountain
What about ochazuke?
Ochazuke?
I can't say.
You're so sweet.
Oh, yes.
And I said ochazuke.
I don't want to do it again.
One point for now.
I only heard "kind" and "oatmeal".
Maybe no one else said it.
I wonder.
What? I don't know what to say.
When I saw the picture or something...
Bangs?
I like that.
I like them both.
I don't know.
Heavenly game.
Bangs.
Let's see...
the part where you slide
Why do you say
The part where you eat a lot
I like it.
You're so sweet.
Thank you.
I said you're sweet.
I'm left with a lot of pretentiousness.
I see.
You're funny.
I'll leave it to you.
flirty eyes
A〜〜〜〜〜
The part where you're particular.
Good memory
kind and gentle
the way people call you "kan-chan" (Japanese for "person-chan")
A〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜
I didn't understand
It's so hard!
You call me "Hito-chan", don't you?
I've been calling you Hito-chan lately.
It's difficult
Halomon, one point for you!
Ki-ling-ling.
Thanks to Julien!
What a bunch of idiots Julian is!
It's all about Julian.
Oh, okay? All of you.
I love it here so much, so fast.
It's okay.
Okay.
He's so handsome.
Coconut.
Good-looking guy.
good-looking
Good looking guy.
Long legs.
Who said that?Did anyone say anything?
Thirteen.
That's funny. We're gonna do it again.
I thought for sure someone said it.
I'm sure someone said something about your style.
What?
I guess they didn't think they had to.
Okay, OK.
Okay, I'll have another one, please. Ready? Ready?
I don't want to! You look so bright!
Oh, is that a mocking face?
Oh, my God, it doesn't even start at the top.
He's so handsome, with a scowl on his face.
Ha~~n
Ah~.
Aiki-chan, you know, you once told me what you liked about me.
This is it.
He takes the lead.
Ah~.
Wrong.
It's different. I didn't think of it, but he told me.
He has a loud voice.
Oh, no.
Ah~.
I wonder...
It's fun.
Hey, have fun.
Ah.
Kabami.
I was so surprised and amazed that I fell in love with it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What do you mean?
But I saw it in a video before.
I was surprised and astonished.
I don't know. Is it my eyes?
Oh, my God. You like it?
No, you're surprised. Look at those eyes. I wonder what's wrong with Hito-chan.
I don't know. Two points for now.
Yes. Good looking. Outline.
You have a good point. Thank you.
I was a good-looking guy, too.
I was wearing a good-looking headdress.
Sweat, too?
You were wearing a headdress? No way.
I was wearing cheeks.
Cheeks?
My cheeks.
Why were you surprised?
Your cheeks are so soft.
Oh, squeeze them.
It makes me nervous.
That's what TikTok is... soft.
Cheeks.
I thought someone would say "Stylie.
I'm going to say it.
I'm gonna go stretch my legs a little bit more.
Next, Julia.
Julia.
Here we go.
Wait, it's Julia.
Wait a minute.
Julia, right?
Here we go.
Ready.
Julia's.
Wait a minute.
I'll do it again.
Did you hear that?
I heard it.
It wasn't on.
I wasn't set.
I probably wasn't wearing it.
Let's do it again.
Change it.
I won't change.
I don't know how to put it in one word.
Okay?
Yeah, I'm ready.
Ready.
Here we go.
Attach.
Free. Shape of the mouth. Correct.
My pace.
Eyelashes.
I didn't say the one that came to mind. That's fine. Okay, I'll do the second one.
Ready. Free.
Shape of the mouth.
I can only hear you.
I'm sorry.
I heard a strange voice.
I know this place, Haru.
Got it?
Isn't it really loud?
You've never seen it before?
I have no idea.
I have no idea.I don't get it.
Diagonal?
You say that?
Secret.
I think I remember the end.
I don't know.
I like one thing about it.
I see what you mean.
Well, you're right.
Next.
Oshuko.
Great.
But the sentence is wrong.
Is this Arby's?
Did someone say they like it?
OK, then.
What? Erwin didn't answer again? His mouth is a little free.
Free.
Okay, Hiori.
Didn't you hear me? Didn't you hear me?
No, thank you. Very well.
I didn't understand.
Let me try to say it in one word.
Eyelashes.
Okay, now that I've used the best part, let's do it one more time.
Oh, yeah.
Next, curves.
Ah, yes.
Dance.
You're right!
That's amazing!
That's great!
Can you hear me? Dance?
I didn't hear you.
What did Pio say?
Gap.
Great. Four points.
Pal is free.
Did you guess the rest?
Yes, I did.
That's great!
She guessed two.
Bye-bye!
Okay?
Okay. - Okay.
Yes, I'm ready.
Let's do this.
Okay, let's do it.
Ready?
Gao.
Q. What are the characteristics? A. Kissidomamboku.
Q. What is the application of xidmambok? A. Ping pong
Q. What are the ears of Xidmamboku? A. Link
Wait a minute longer, there's no xidambonbok in there.
Let's stop.
I had to get out, I told you.
I asked for it.
There's one more.
One more time, please.
Wait a minute.
Ready.
Fluffy.
Correct.
To Mom.
Somehow, it's going round and round. Something.
Julia.
Fluffy. Fluffy.
Ah, I heard it. But why did I hear it?
Outline.
Subscribe to our channel!
See you soon!
See you!
See you later, Hana!
Dobo, I knew it! An mosquito!
Mayuken Dobo's body
Mayuken, new body
Dobo's steps
What? Already, the main force was too strong.
The volume of your voice.
What?
The specifics.
Length of hair.
Uh, yeah.
I like it.
Okay, then. Answer.
Correct answer.
Nose.
Will you go out?
Oh, you're going out.
Fluffy
Face
Ding dong ding dong
It didn't reach me.
why?
I have to askI have to ask.
I have to listen.
I feel like I'm being told something
I feel like I can hear you.
I heard you, Risa-chan.
I can hear you when we're next to each other.
It's difficult.
The winner is...
Julia.
Wow!
Julia has 4 points.
Hiyorin, Hitokoto and
Kanabin got 2 points, and Aki-chan and I got 1 point.
It's so hard!
It was painful!
Lastly, we would like to give a super-sized shame-eating image to the Sendai club members.
Please comment on it!
Okay, here we go!
Aaaaah!
That's why!
So!
by H.
The part where you love us.
Super sweet.
Yes, maybe a little too much love
Smile
Always with us
Loves us all
I got it in the end.
I didn't get it at first.
Was I right?
You were right.